Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1980-2014; Series 9
  - Francis Criss - Venue - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 2001 August 4-October 14; Series 9 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Francis Criss: Venue-Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2001 August 4-October 14; Series 9 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Francis Criss - Shipping, 2001 August 4-October 14; Series 9 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Francis Criss - Condition Reports, 2001 August 4-October 14; Series 9 (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Linda Bessemer, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Marcel Dzama, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Ken Feingold, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Kojo Griffen, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Tim Hawkinson, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Bruce Nauman, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Nigel Poor, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Susan Smith-Pinelo, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Artist Bruce Yonemoto, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Shipping, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Deinstallation/Shipping, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - 47th Biennial Exhibition: Fantasy Underfoot - Installation Photos, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 9 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Aquavella Galleries, New York and Reno, NV, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Mme Sylvie Balthazart - Eon, Paris, France, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Broad Art Foundation, Santa Monica, CA, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Chase Tower, Houston, TX, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: M. Marcel Elefant, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Fundacio Joan Miro, Barcelona, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Fundacio Pilar I Joan Miro a Mallorca, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro's Painted Sculpture - Lender: La Caixa, Barcelona, Spain, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, TX, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Lender: Thomas Ammann Fine Art, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Condition Reports, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Checklists/Crate List, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Deinstallation, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Installation, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Packing/Unpacking Images, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Tour, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Tour: Portland Art Museum, Oregon, 28 June-21 September 2003; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Tour: Salvador Dali Museum, St. Petersburg, FL, 1 February-4 May 2002; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - The Shape of Color: Joan Miro - Shipping, 2002 September 21-2003 January 6; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Addison Gallery of American Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Arthur Ross Foundation, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Bacher, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Baltimore Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Childs Gallery, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Columbia, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Coughlan, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Grolier, Davis, and Columbia, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Domenici/Denker, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Glen Burnie Historic House, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Goley, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Grolier Club Venue, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Hughes, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Indianapolis Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Larkin, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Lauren Rogers Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Library of Congress, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Maier Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Mary Lublin Fine Arts, Inc., 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Mead Art Museum, Amherst College, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Meizlik/Denker, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 42)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Metropolitan Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 43)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: National Gallery of Art/Grolier Club, NY, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 44)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: National Gallery of Art Library, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 45)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Neville-Strass, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 46)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: New Britain Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 47)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Paige, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 48)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Philadelphia Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 49)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: Westmoreland Museum of Art, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 50)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Lender: William P. Carl Fine Arts, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 51)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Returns - Not Travelling, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 52)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Shipping, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 53)
  - Whistler and His Circle in Venice - Travelling Exhibition, 2003 February 8-May 5; Series 9 (Box 89, Folder 54)
  - Jasper Johns to Jeff Koons: Four Decades of Art from the Broad Collections, 2002 March 17-June 2; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Johns, Jasper - Untitled, Lichtenstein, Roy - Mirror #1, 2002 March 17-June 2; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Jasper Johns to Jeff Koons: Four Decades of Art from the Broad Collections, 2002 March 17-June 2; Series 9 (Box 90, Folders 3-4)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Checklists/Crate - lists, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Fernandez, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Ferrato, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Cobb, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Frampton, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Gore, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Leibovitz, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Mark, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Reed, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Rodriguez, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Shell, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Walker, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Venue - Manchester Craftsman's Guild, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America - Lender: Venue - LA Public Library, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness in America, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 9 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Poetry and Alchemy: Selected Prints of Joseph Goldyne, 2001 October 6-December 17; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Laces, 2001 November 3-February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Tapestries, 2001 November 3-February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Lichtenstein and Beyond: Recent Acquisitions of Modern Prints, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Heart Nouveau: Valentine Prints by Lou Stovall, 2001 December 15-2002 March 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Stanley Tretick: The Kennedy Years, 2002 July 1-November 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folders 6-10)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Shipping, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Paintings, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Clocks, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism: The William A. Clark Collection - Ceramics, 2001 December 8-2002 February 4; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Celebrating the Legacy II, February-May 2001; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Art and Economics: Sienese Paintings from the Dawn of the Financial Age - Shipping Arrangements, 2002 July 31-2002 October 14; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Art and Economics: Sienese Painting-Shipping Arrangements, 2002 July 31-2002 October 14; Series 9 (Box 91, Folders 18-19)
  - Here is New York: A Democracy of Photographs, 2002 September 7-2002 November 11; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Picturing the Corcoran's Sculpture: Photographs by David Finn, 2002 November 3-December 30; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Picturing the Corcoran's Sculpture: Photographs by David Finn - Exhibition Preparation, 2002 November 3-December 30; Series 9 (Box 91, Folders 22-23)
  - Picturing the Corcoran's Sculpture: Photographs by David Finn - Shipping Information, 2002 November 3-December 30; Series 9 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Beyond the Frame, Impressionism Revisited-The Sculptures of J. Seward Johnson, Jr., 2003 September 13-2004 January 5; Series 9 (Box 91, Folders 25-27)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Checklist w/ Values, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Checklist w/out Values, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Installation/Packing, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Condition Reports, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Collection Shipping, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Itinerary, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Checklist, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Cratelist, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Vintage Prints Removed From Exhibition, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Johanna Fiore, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Gordon Parks, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Center for African American History and Cult, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Cone Laumont Editions LTD., 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Schomburg Center for Research in Black, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Photographic Archives, U. of Louisville, KY, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Lender: Richard Powell and C.T. Woods-Powell, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Slides and Photographs, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Exhibition Materials Notebook, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Dispersal Shipping, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Corcoran General, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Restrictions, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Minnesota Museum of American Art, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Museum of the City of New York, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Insurance, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Linda's Travel File to MCNY, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Milwaukee Art Museum, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Detroit Institute of Arts, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Ulrich Museum, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Norton Museum of Art, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Michael C. Carlos Museum, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: California African American Museum, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Condition Reports for Photos Removed from Exhibition, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Damage, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Inter-Museum Shipping, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - New Orleans Museum of Art, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Cincinnati Art Museum, 2001 February 16-May 6; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: The Oakland Museum of California, 2001 June 23-September 23; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art, 2001 October 20-2002 January 13; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Dixon Gallery and Gardens, 2002 February 30-April 7; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Hudson River Museum, 2002 June 7-September 1; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Tacoma Art Museum, 2002 September 28-2003 January 5; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: George Eastman House, 2003 February-April; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: The Newark Museum, 2003 June 3-August 31; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: William Benton Museum of Art, 2003 October 18-December 20; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks - Venue: Chicago Historical Society, 2004 February 14-May 2; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - Gordon Parks: Selections from the Collection of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, exhibition at Dallas Museum of Fine Arts - Condition reports, 2005 June 5-September 4; Series 9 (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - Gordon Parks: Selections from the Collection of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, exhibition at Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 2005 June 5-September 4; Series 9 (Box 92, Folders 47-48)
  - Andre Kertesz and Theodore Fried: Away From Home - Rotunda, 2001 July 21-September 17; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Rhapsodies in Black: Art of the Harlem Renaissance - Installation Slides Only, 1998 April 11-June 22; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Phoenix Art Museum, 2000 July 29-September 24; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Tour Shipping, 2000 July 29-September 24; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Texas, Woman's Museum, 2000; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - International Center for Photography, 2000 October 16-2001 January 2; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Miami Art Museum, 2001 January 17-April 15; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Seattle Art Museum, 2001 September 20-2002 January 6; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Friends of Photography, 2002 May 8-July 15; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Checklists, 2000-2002; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Damaged and Destroyed at Texas Woman's Museum, Lamis Srour, 2000-2002; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Correspondence with the Studio, 2000-2002; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women - Installation Views, Corcoran Venue, 2000-2002; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - The 46th Biennial Exhibition: Media Metaphor, 2000 December 9-2001 March 5; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Native Land: Photographs from the Robert Lewis Collection - Gallery 1, 2001 May 12-July 30; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - FIVA 2001 - Gallery 15, 2001 June 6-July 9; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Saints and Sinners: Observations on the Sacred and the Profane, 2001 June 6-July 9; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - In Responce to Place: Photographs from the Nature Conservancy's Last Great Places, 2001 September 15-December 31; Series 9 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Primary Properties: Joseph Dumbacher, John Dumbacher, Mary Judge - Gallery 1, 2001 September 29-December 10; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Confronting Nature: Icelandic Art of the 20th Century, 2001 October 14-November 26; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Insurance, Shipping, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Venue: Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Disbursal, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Extension (1 Week), 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Robert Abrams, New York, NY, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Anderson Gallery, Lenders: Lauro and Lilliana Accorsi, Buffalo, NY, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Stanley Bard, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Collection Musee National d'Art Moderne, Centre de Georges Pompidou, Paris, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Cheekwood Museum, Nashville TX, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Larry Rivers: Art and the Artist - Lender: Hirshhorn Museum, 2002; Series 9 (Box 100, Folder 13)